[{"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "Is there a refrigerator in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "Is there a guitar in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [48]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [60, 61, 62, 89, 90, 91, 93, 94, 116, 142, 145, 146, 149, 152, 155, 158, 165, 167, 169, 170, 171, 173, 174, 175, 176, 177, 178, 182, 185, 186, 187, 188], "object_names": ["object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object"], "question": "Is there a object in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [60, 61, 62, 89, 90, 91, 93, 94, 116, 142, 145, 146, 149, 152, 155, 158, 165, 167, 169, 170, 171, 173, 174, 175, 176, 177, 178, 182, 185, 186, 187, 188]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [168, 180, 197], "object_names": ["towel", "towel", "towel"], "question": "Is there a towel in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168, 180, 197]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28], "object_names": ["wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall"], "question": "Is there a wall in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [181], "object_names": ["pot"], "question": "Is there a pot in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [181]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [147, 154], "object_names": ["cup", "cup"], "question": "Is there a cup in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147, 154]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "Is there a chair in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [68]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [98], "object_names": ["computer"], "question": "Is there a computer in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [98]}, {"answers": ["Yes.", "Yes, there is."], "object_ids": [67], "object_names": ["case"], "question": "Is there a case in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [67]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [57], "object_names": ["shelf"], "question": "How many shelfs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [57]}, {"answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [19, 63], "object_names": ["backpack", "backpack"], "question": "How many backpacks are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19, 63]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "How many bicycles are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [58]}, {"answers": ["3"], "object_ids": [13, 14, 15], "object_names": ["bin", "bin", "bin"], "question": "How many bins are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13, 14, 15]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "How many guitars are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [48]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [52], "object_names": ["dish rack"], "question": "How many dish racks are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [52]}, {"answers": ["5"], "object_ids": [92, 111, 118, 138, 172], "object_names": ["paper", "paper", "paper", "paper", "paper"], "question": "How many papers are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [92, 111, 118, 138, 172]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "How many beds are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38]}, {"answers": ["32"], "object_ids": [60, 61, 62, 89, 90, 91, 93, 94, 116, 142, 145, 146, 149, 152, 155, 158, 165, 167, 169, 170, 171, 173, 174, 175, 176, 177, 178, 182, 185, 186, 187, 188], "object_names": ["object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object", "object"], "question": "How many objects are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [60, 61, 62, 89, 90, 91, 93, 94, 116, 142, 145, 146, 149, 152, 155, 158, 165, 167, 169, 170, 171, 173, 174, 175, 176, 177, 178, 182, 185, 186, 187, 188]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "How many clocks are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [10], "object_names": ["floor"], "question": "How many floors are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [10]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "How many lamps are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [189]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [33], "object_names": ["couch"], "question": "How many couchs are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [33]}, {"answers": ["9"], "object_ids": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28], "object_names": ["wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall", "wall"], "question": "How many walls are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [181], "object_names": ["pot"], "question": "How many pots are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [181]}, {"answers": ["3"], "object_ids": [3, 35, 36], "object_names": ["table", "table", "table"], "question": "How many tables are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3, 35, 36]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [56], "object_names": ["ceiling"], "question": "How many ceilings are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [56]}, {"answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [183, 184], "object_names": ["bowl", "bowl"], "question": "How many bowls are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [183, 184]}, {"answers": ["1"], "object_ids": [46], "object_names": ["oven"], "question": "How many ovens are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [46]}, {"answers": ["2"], "object_ids": [147, 154], "object_names": ["cup", "cup"], "question": "How many cups are there in the room?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147, 154]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [3], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood or similar. Its size is relatively large. Its placement is horizontal. Its state is good condition. Its function is used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood or similar. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood or similar. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood or similar. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal. Its state is good condition. Its function is used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["laminated panel or quartz", "Stone"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["near the wall"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["serves as a workspace for preparing food and placing kitchen supplies"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [4], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["near the wall"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is laminated panel or quartz. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is serves as a workspace for preparing food and placing kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4]}, {"answers": ["brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is laminated panel or quartz. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is near the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is serves as a workspace for preparing food and placing kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is laminated panel or quartz. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is near the wall. Its function is serves as a workspace for preparing food and placing kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4]}, {"answers": ["serves as a workspace for preparing food and placing kitchen supplies"], "object_ids": [4], "object_names": ["counter"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is laminated panel or quartz. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is near the wall. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [4]}, {"answers": ["transparent", "Transparent"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["glass", "Glass"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["light", "Light"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["against the wall"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides a contained space for showering"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides a contained space for showering"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass. Its weight is light. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against the wall. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5]}, {"answers": ["transparent", "Transparent"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass. Its weight is light. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is provides a contained space for showering. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its material is glass. Its weight is light. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is provides a contained space for showering. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5]}, {"answers": ["against the wall"], "object_ids": [5], "object_names": ["shower"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is transparent. Its texture is smooth. Its material is glass. Its weight is light. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is provides a contained space for showering. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [5]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is smooth. Its material is cotton or polyester fiber. Its placement is hanging vertically from the ceiling. Its state is good condition, no tears or stains. Its function is blocks light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is smooth. Its size is moderate. Its placement is hanging vertically from the ceiling. Its state is good condition, no tears or stains. Its function is blocks light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is smooth. Its material is cotton or polyester fiber. Its size is moderate. Its placement is hanging vertically from the ceiling. Its function is blocks light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is smooth. Its material is cotton or polyester fiber. Its size is moderate. Its placement is hanging vertically from the ceiling. Its state is good condition, no tears or stains. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is semi-transparent fabric. Its material is fabric. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is blocks light from entering the room. Its function is blocks the light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is semi-transparent fabric. Its material is fabric. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hangs vertically on the window. Its state is blocks light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is semi-transparent fabric. Its material is fabric. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hangs vertically on the window. Its state is blocks light from entering the room. Its function is blocks the light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7], "object_names": ["curtain"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light-colored. Its texture is semi-transparent fabric. Its size is standard-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hangs vertically on the window. Its state is blocks light from entering the room. Its function is blocks the light from entering the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wooden"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["pine or similar wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["against the wall"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used for computer tasks"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [8], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is wooden. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against the wall. Its function is used for computer tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is wooden. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against the wall. Its function is used for computer tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8]}, {"answers": ["wooden"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is against the wall. Its function is used for computer tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8]}, {"answers": ["against the wall"], "object_ids": [8], "object_names": ["desk"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is wooden. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its function is used for computer tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [8]}, {"answers": ["N/A"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["N/A"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood (likely oak or similar type)", "Wood"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["N/A"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["snugly fits against the wall"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["suitable for storing various items including books, electronic devices, and other household essentials"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is N/A. Its texture is N/A. Its material is wood (likely oak or similar type). Its weight is N/A. Its size is moderate. Its placement is snugly fits against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is suitable for storing various items including books, electronic devices, and other household essentials. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9]}, {"answers": ["N/A"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is N/A. Its texture is N/A. Its material is wood (likely oak or similar type). Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is snugly fits against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is suitable for storing various items including books, electronic devices, and other household essentials. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9]}, {"answers": ["snugly fits against the wall"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is N/A. Its texture is N/A. Its material is wood (likely oak or similar type). Its weight is N/A. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is suitable for storing various items including books, electronic devices, and other household essentials. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9]}, {"answers": ["N/A"], "object_ids": [9], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is N/A. Its material is wood (likely oak or similar type). Its weight is N/A. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is snugly fits against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is suitable for storing various items including books, electronic devices, and other household essentials. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [9]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["porcelain", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically against the wall"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides a space for handwashing and personal hygiene tasks"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is porcelain. Its size is medium. Its shape is round. Its placement is vertically against the wall. Its function is provides a space for handwashing and personal hygiene tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11]}, {"answers": ["vertically against the wall"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is porcelain. Its size is medium. Its shape is round. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides a space for handwashing and personal hygiene tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11]}, {"answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is porcelain. Its size is medium. Its placement is vertically against the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides a space for handwashing and personal hygiene tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [11], "object_names": ["sink"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is porcelain. Its size is medium. Its shape is round. Its placement is vertically against the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides a space for handwashing and personal hygiene tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [11]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic and metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["horizontal on tiled floor, leaning against the wall"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-maintained and fully functional"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["measures weight"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-maintained and fully functional"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic and metal. Its weight is standard. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal on tiled floor, leaning against the wall. Its function is measures weight. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12]}, {"answers": ["plastic and metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its weight is standard. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal on tiled floor, leaning against the wall. Its state is well-maintained and fully functional. Its function is measures weight. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic and metal. Its weight is standard. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal on tiled floor, leaning against the wall. Its state is well-maintained and fully functional. Its function is measures weight. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [12], "object_names": ["scale"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic and metal. Its weight is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal on tiled floor, leaning against the wall. Its state is well-maintained and fully functional. Its function is measures weight. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [12]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular with rounded edges", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["sits on the floor"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used for storing clothes or other items"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular with rounded edges. Its placement is sits on the floor. Its state is standing upright. Its function is used for storing clothes or other items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its shape is rectangular with rounded edges. Its placement is sits on the floor. Its state is standing upright. Its function is used for storing clothes or other items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["rectangular with rounded edges", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is relatively small. Its placement is sits on the floor. Its state is standing upright. Its function is used for storing clothes or other items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["sits on the floor"], "object_ids": [13], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular with rounded edges. Its state is standing upright. Its function is used for storing clothes or other items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["serving as a container for rubbish"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [14], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is serving as a container for rubbish. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is next to a door. Its function is serving as a container for rubbish. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is next to a door. Its state is slightly ajar. Its function is serving as a container for rubbish. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["serving as a container for rubbish"], "object_ids": [14], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is next to a door. Its state is slightly ajar. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [15], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth, glossy. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is storing small items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth, glossy. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on the floor, leaning against a wooden board. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth, glossy. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on the floor, leaning against a wooden board. Its state is good condition. Its function is storing small items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15], "object_names": ["bin"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on the floor, leaning against a wooden board. Its state is good condition. Its function is storing small items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": [null], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": [null], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically on a wooden cabinet"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["turned off"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides the best viewing angle"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically on a wooden cabinet"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is None. Its material is plastic. Its weight is None. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is turned off. Its function is provides the best viewing angle. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16]}, {"answers": ["provides the best viewing angle"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is None. Its material is plastic. Its weight is None. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on a wooden cabinet. Its state is turned off. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16]}, {"answers": [null], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is None. Its material is plastic. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on a wooden cabinet. Its state is turned off. Its function is provides the best viewing angle. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [16], "object_names": ["tv"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is None. Its material is plastic. Its weight is None. Its size is standard. Its placement is vertically on a wooden cabinet. Its state is turned off. Its function is provides the best viewing angle. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [16]}, {"answers": ["brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["velvety"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["large", "Large"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["leaning against a wooden headboard"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides support and comfort for anyone lying in bed"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["large", "Large"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is brown. Its texture is velvety. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a wooden headboard. Its function is provides support and comfort for anyone lying in bed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17]}, {"answers": ["brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is velvety. Its size is large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a wooden headboard. Its function is provides support and comfort for anyone lying in bed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17]}, {"answers": ["provides support and comfort for anyone lying in bed"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is brown. Its texture is velvety. Its size is large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a wooden headboard. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17]}, {"answers": ["velvety"], "object_ids": [17], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is brown. Its size is large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a wooden headboard. Its function is provides support and comfort for anyone lying in bed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [17]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["displaying time"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its placement is hangs vertically on the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is displaying time. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18]}, {"answers": ["displaying time"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is round. Its placement is hangs vertically on the wall. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is round. Its placement is hangs vertically on the wall. Its function is displaying time. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [18], "object_names": ["clock"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is round. Its placement is hangs vertically on the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is displaying time. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [18]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [19], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black or dark brown. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a blue chair. Its state is good condition. Its function is has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black or dark brown. Its material is nylon or canvas. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a blue chair. Its state is good condition. Its function is has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black or dark brown. Its material is nylon or canvas. Its size is medium. Its placement is leaning against a blue chair. Its state is good condition. Its function is has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black or dark brown. Its material is nylon or canvas. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is leaning against a blue chair. Its function is has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its weight is moderate. Its size is moderate. Its shape is round seat, four legs. Its placement is upright next to the table. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is round seat, four legs. Its placement is upright next to the table. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides casual seating or footstool. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its material is wood. Its weight is moderate. Its size is moderate. Its shape is round seat, four legs. Its placement is upright next to the table. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides casual seating or footstool. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its weight is moderate. Its shape is round seat, four legs. Its placement is upright next to the table. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides casual seating or footstool. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard height for sitting at a kitchen bar or a bar counter", "Medium"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["placed vertically next to a table"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides seating"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [30], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is wood. Its size is standard height for sitting at a kitchen bar or a bar counter. Its shape is round seat. Its placement is placed vertically next to a table. Its function is provides seating. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its size is standard height for sitting at a kitchen bar or a bar counter. Its shape is round seat. Its placement is placed vertically next to a table. Its function is provides seating. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30]}, {"answers": ["provides seating"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its material is wood. Its size is standard height for sitting at a kitchen bar or a bar counter. Its shape is round seat. Its placement is placed vertically next to a table. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30]}, {"answers": ["placed vertically next to a table"], "object_ids": [30], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its material is wood. Its size is standard height for sitting at a kitchen bar or a bar counter. Its shape is round seat. Its function is provides seating. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its size is medium. Its shape is round seat. Its placement is sits vertically on the floor. Its state is empty. Its function is providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is round seat. Its state is empty. Its function is providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is round seat. Its placement is sits vertically on the floor. Its state is empty. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is wood. Its size is medium. Its shape is round seat. Its placement is sits vertically on the floor. Its state is empty. Its function is providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["pine or similar wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round seat and four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright on the floor"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-preserved"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["seating"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is smooth. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its shape is round seat and four legs. Its placement is upright on the floor. Its state is well-preserved. Its function is seating. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [32]}, {"answers": ["seating"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is smooth. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is round seat and four legs. Its placement is upright on the floor. Its state is well-preserved. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [32]}, {"answers": ["round seat and four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its texture is smooth. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its size is moderate. Its placement is upright on the floor. Its state is well-preserved. Its function is seating. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [32]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [32], "object_names": ["stool"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood color. Its material is pine or similar wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is round seat and four legs. Its placement is upright on the floor. Its state is well-preserved. Its function is seating. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [32]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["stainless steel or similar material", "Metal"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard dimensions for a household refrigerator", "Large"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["large, rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically positioned on the floor"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used to store food"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically positioned on the floor"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is stainless steel or similar material. Its size is standard dimensions for a household refrigerator. Its shape is large, rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is used to store food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34]}, {"answers": ["used to store food"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is stainless steel or similar material. Its size is standard dimensions for a household refrigerator. Its shape is large, rectangular. Its placement is vertically positioned on the floor. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is stainless steel or similar material. Its size is standard dimensions for a household refrigerator. Its shape is large, rectangular. Its placement is vertically positioned on the floor. Its function is used to store food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34]}, {"answers": ["stainless steel or similar material", "Metal"], "object_ids": [34], "object_names": ["refrigerator"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its size is standard dimensions for a household refrigerator. Its shape is large, rectangular. Its placement is vertically positioned on the floor. Its state is closed. Its function is used to store food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [34]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft and velvety"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["velvet", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically on a beige carpet"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is soft and velvety. Its material is velvet. Its size is relatively large. Its placement is vertically on a beige carpet. Its state is in great condition. Its function is can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["soft and velvety"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is velvet. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on a beige carpet. Its state is in great condition. Its function is can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is soft and velvety. Its material is velvet. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on a beige carpet. Its function is can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table"], "object_ids": [35], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is soft and velvety. Its material is velvet. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on a beige carpet. Its state is in great condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [36], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is smooth. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on a tiled floor. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is used to put objects on top. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wooden. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on a tiled floor. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is used to put objects on top. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wooden. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on a tiled floor. Its function is used to put objects on top. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36], "object_names": ["table"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wooden. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is on a tiled floor. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is used to put objects on top. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["porcelain or similar material", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["oval", "Circular"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically positioned along the wall"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard toilet with a side flushing mechanism"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is porcelain or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is oval. Its placement is vertically positioned along the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is standard toilet with a side flushing mechanism. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is porcelain or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is oval. Its placement is vertically positioned along the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is standard toilet with a side flushing mechanism. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is porcelain or similar material. Its shape is oval. Its placement is vertically positioned along the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is standard toilet with a side flushing mechanism. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [37], "object_names": ["toilet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is porcelain or similar material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is oval. Its placement is vertically positioned along the wall. Its function is standard toilet with a side flushing mechanism. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [37]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cozy"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["comfortable for one person", "Small"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["horizontal against the wall"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["providing a place to rest and sleep"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["comfortable for one person", "Small"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is cozy. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal against the wall. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is providing a place to rest and sleep. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38]}, {"answers": ["horizontal against the wall"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is cozy. Its material is wood. Its size is comfortable for one person. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is providing a place to rest and sleep. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is cozy. Its size is comfortable for one person. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal against the wall. Its state is well-maintained. Its function is providing a place to rest and sleep. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [38], "object_names": ["bed"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is cozy. Its material is wood. Its size is comfortable for one person. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is horizontal against the wall. Its function is providing a place to rest and sleep. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [38]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically against the wall"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides ample storage space"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides ample storage space"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically against the wall. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is provides ample storage space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is provides ample storage space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39]}, {"answers": ["vertically against the wall"], "object_ids": [39], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is relatively large. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is provides ample storage space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [39]}, {"answers": ["clean white", "White"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["fabric or similar material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standing vertically against the wall"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides privacy and organization, maximizes use of space"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["clean white", "White"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is fabric or similar material. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is provides privacy and organization, maximizes use of space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clean white. Its material is fabric or similar material. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing vertically against the wall. Its function is provides privacy and organization, maximizes use of space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40]}, {"answers": ["standing vertically against the wall"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clean white. Its material is fabric or similar material. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is provides privacy and organization, maximizes use of space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [40], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is clean white. Its material is fabric or similar material. Its size is medium-sized. Its placement is standing vertically against the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is provides privacy and organization, maximizes use of space. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [40]}, {"answers": ["natural light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["larger than similar items", "Large"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically on the countertop"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["storage unit for essential kitchen items"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural light brown. Its size is larger than similar items. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on the countertop. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage unit for essential kitchen items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [41]}, {"answers": ["larger than similar items", "Large"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural light brown. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on the countertop. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage unit for essential kitchen items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [41]}, {"answers": ["storage unit for essential kitchen items"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is larger than similar items. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically on the countertop. Its state is in good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [41]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [41], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural light brown. Its material is wood. Its size is larger than similar items. Its placement is vertically on the countertop. Its state is in good condition. Its function is storage unit for essential kitchen items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [41]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood (pine or oak)", "Wood"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wall-mounted"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["storage for everyday items"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood (pine or oak)", "Wood"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is wall-mounted. Its state is closed. Its function is storage for everyday items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42]}, {"answers": ["wall-mounted"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood (pine or oak). Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is storage for everyday items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is wood (pine or oak). Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is wall-mounted. Its state is closed. Its function is storage for everyday items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [42], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its material is wood (pine or oak). Its size is medium-sized. Its placement is wall-mounted. Its state is closed. Its function is storage for everyday items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [42]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wooden"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright on countertop"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["stores kitchen supplies"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [43], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is wooden. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on countertop. Its state is closed. Its function is stores kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is wooden. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on countertop. Its function is stores kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is wooden. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on countertop. Its state is closed. Its function is stores kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [43], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light brown. Its texture is wooden. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on countertop. Its state is closed. Its function is stores kitchen supplies. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [43]}, {"answers": ["natural wood", "Brown"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood grain"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["serves as a standard storage cabinet, suitable for storing kitchen utensils or other household items"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["serves as a standard storage cabinet, suitable for storing kitchen utensils or other household items"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood. Its texture is wood grain. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on the wall. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44]}, {"answers": ["natural wood", "Brown"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is wood grain. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is serves as a standard storage cabinet, suitable for storing kitchen utensils or other household items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood. Its texture is wood grain. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is serves as a standard storage cabinet, suitable for storing kitchen utensils or other household items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [44], "object_names": ["cabinet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is natural wood. Its texture is wood grain. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on the wall. Its state is closed. Its function is serves as a standard storage cabinet, suitable for storing kitchen utensils or other household items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [44]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["mesh or net structure"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["mesh or net structure", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cylindrical", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["stands vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["for general household use"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["mesh or net structure", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is mesh or net structure. Its size is medium. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is stands vertically on the floor. Its function is for general household use. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [47]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is mesh or net structure. Its material is mesh or net structure. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is stands vertically on the floor. Its function is for general household use. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [47]}, {"answers": ["mesh or net structure"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is mesh or net structure. Its size is medium. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is stands vertically on the floor. Its function is for general household use. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [47]}, {"answers": ["for general household use"], "object_ids": [47], "object_names": ["basket"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its texture is mesh or net structure. Its material is mesh or net structure. Its size is medium. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is stands vertically on the floor. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [47]}, {"answers": ["rich reddish-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rosewood or cedar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hollow body", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["leaning against the wall"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard acoustic guitar with six strings and a tuning knob"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is rich reddish-brown. Its material is rosewood or cedar. Its size is moderate. Its shape is hollow body. Its placement is leaning against the wall. Its function is standard acoustic guitar with six strings and a tuning knob. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [48]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is rich reddish-brown. Its material is rosewood or cedar. Its shape is hollow body. Its placement is leaning against the wall. Its state is great condition. Its function is standard acoustic guitar with six strings and a tuning knob. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [48]}, {"answers": ["rich reddish-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is rosewood or cedar. Its size is moderate. Its shape is hollow body. Its placement is leaning against the wall. Its state is great condition. Its function is standard acoustic guitar with six strings and a tuning knob. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [48]}, {"answers": ["leaning against the wall"], "object_ids": [48], "object_names": ["guitar"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is rich reddish-brown. Its material is rosewood or cedar. Its size is moderate. Its shape is hollow body. Its state is great condition. Its function is standard acoustic guitar with six strings and a tuning knob. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [48]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["paper or cloth", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standing upright on a white table"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["storing tissues"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["storing tissues"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft. Its material is paper or cloth. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright on a white table. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49]}, {"answers": ["paper or cloth", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright on a white table. Its state is closed. Its function is storing tissues. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on a white table"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft. Its material is paper or cloth. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is storing tissues. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [49], "object_names": ["tissue box"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft. Its material is paper or cloth. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is standing upright on a white table. Its state is closed. Its function is storing tissues. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [49]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [50], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is grainy. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically against a wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is storage. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is grainy. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically against a wall. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is grainy. Its material is wood. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is storage. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50], "object_names": ["stand"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is grainy. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertically against a wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is storage. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["shiny"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lightweight", "Light"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["toasts bread"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["toasts bread"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is shiny. Its material is metal. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [54]}, {"answers": ["metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is shiny. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright. Its state is closed. Its function is toasts bread. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [54]}, {"answers": ["shiny"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is metal. Its weight is lightweight. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright. Its state is closed. Its function is toasts bread. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [54]}, {"answers": ["lightweight", "Light"], "object_ids": [54], "object_names": ["toaster"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is shiny. Its material is metal. Its size is rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright. Its state is closed. Its function is toasts bread. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [54]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["installed vertically"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides entry and security"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is installed vertically. Its state is closed. Its function is provides entry and security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [55]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is installed vertically. Its state is closed. Its function is provides entry and security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [55]}, {"answers": ["installed vertically"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is closed. Its function is provides entry and security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [55]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [55], "object_names": ["door"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is installed vertically. Its state is closed. Its function is provides entry and security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [55]}, {"answers": ["gray with red accents", "Red"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [58], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["aluminum", "Metal"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [58], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [58], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["leaning against the curtain"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [58], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["suitable for everyday use"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [58], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["leaning against the curtain"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray with red accents. Its material is aluminum. Its size is medium. Its function is suitable for everyday use. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [58]}, {"answers": ["aluminum", "Metal"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray with red accents. Its size is medium. Its placement is leaning against the curtain. Its function is suitable for everyday use. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [58]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray with red accents. Its material is aluminum. Its placement is leaning against the curtain. Its function is suitable for everyday use. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [58]}, {"answers": ["suitable for everyday use"], "object_ids": [58], "object_names": ["bicycle"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray with red accents. Its material is aluminum. Its size is medium. Its placement is leaning against the curtain. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [58]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["synthetic and leather", "Leather"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic and leather. Its size is standard. Its shape is rounded toe. Its placement is vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right. Its function is suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic and leather. Its size is standard. Its placement is vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right. Its state is good condition. Its function is suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic and leather. Its size is standard. Its shape is rounded toe. Its placement is vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right. Its state is good condition. Its function is suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [59], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic and leather. Its shape is rounded toe. Its placement is vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right. Its state is good condition. Its function is suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["black and gray", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["fabric and metal", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["small"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["folded", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["tucked away in a corner"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["folded"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides seating when unfolded"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["tucked away in a corner"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black and gray. Its material is fabric and metal. Its size is small. Its shape is folded. Its state is folded. Its function is provides seating when unfolded. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [60]}, {"answers": ["black and gray", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is fabric and metal. Its size is small. Its shape is folded. Its placement is tucked away in a corner. Its state is folded. Its function is provides seating when unfolded. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [60]}, {"answers": ["provides seating when unfolded"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black and gray. Its material is fabric and metal. Its size is small. Its shape is folded. Its placement is tucked away in a corner. Its state is folded. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [60]}, {"answers": ["folded", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [60], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black and gray. Its material is fabric and metal. Its size is small. Its placement is tucked away in a corner. Its state is folded. Its function is provides seating when unfolded. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [60]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["fabric or nylon", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from a wooden structure attached to a cabinet"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used for carrying clothes, toys, or other personal items"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is fabric or nylon. Its size is medium. Its placement is hanging vertically from a wooden structure attached to a cabinet. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for carrying clothes, toys, or other personal items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [61]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is fabric or nylon. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically from a wooden structure attached to a cabinet. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for carrying clothes, toys, or other personal items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [61]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is fabric or nylon. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically from a wooden structure attached to a cabinet. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for carrying clothes, toys, or other personal items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [61]}, {"answers": ["fabric or nylon", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [61], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically from a wooden structure attached to a cabinet. Its state is good condition. Its function is used for carrying clothes, toys, or other personal items. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [61]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark (black or dark grey). Its material is nylon or similar fabric. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted. Its function is suitable for daily commuting and traveling. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark (black or dark grey). Its material is nylon or similar fabric. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted. Its state is looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage. Its function is suitable for daily commuting and traveling. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark (black or dark grey). Its material is nylon or similar fabric. Its size is medium. Its placement is laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted. Its state is looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage. Its function is suitable for daily commuting and traveling. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63], "object_names": ["backpack"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark (black or dark grey). Its material is nylon or similar fabric. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage. Its function is suitable for daily commuting and traveling. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is {'doorframe': 'light brown', 'door': 'white'}. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is closed. Its function is provides security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is {'doorframe': 'light brown', 'door': 'white'}. Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is closed. Its function is provides security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is {'doorframe': 'light brown', 'door': 'white'}. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its function is provides security. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66], "object_names": ["doorframe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is {'doorframe': 'light brown', 'door': 'white'}. Its texture is smooth. Its material is wood. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cushioned"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["metal base", "Metal"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["typical office chair shape", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright in front of a desk"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides support during long periods of sitting"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is cushioned. Its material is metal base. Its weight is medium. Its size is medium. Its shape is typical office chair shape. Its placement is upright in front of a desk. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support during long periods of sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [68]}, {"answers": ["typical office chair shape", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is cushioned. Its material is metal base. Its weight is medium. Its size is medium. Its placement is upright in front of a desk. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support during long periods of sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [68]}, {"answers": ["upright in front of a desk"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is cushioned. Its material is metal base. Its weight is medium. Its size is medium. Its shape is typical office chair shape. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support during long periods of sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [68]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [68], "object_names": ["chair"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is cushioned. Its material is metal base. Its size is medium. Its shape is typical office chair shape. Its placement is upright in front of a desk. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support during long periods of sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [68]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["matte"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["audio output"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["audio output"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is matte. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [88]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is matte. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is good condition. Its function is audio output. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [88]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is matte. Its size is medium. Its placement is vertical. Its state is good condition. Its function is audio output. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [88]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [88], "object_names": ["speaker"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is matte. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is audio output. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [88]}, {"answers": ["black, white, silver", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lying flat on a surface, slightly tilted to one side"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition, no obvious damage or wear"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["typical remote control for television or home entertainment systems"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["black, white, silver", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on a surface, slightly tilted to one side. Its state is good condition, no obvious damage or wear. Its function is typical remote control for television or home entertainment systems. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [121]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, silver. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on a surface, slightly tilted to one side. Its state is good condition, no obvious damage or wear. Its function is typical remote control for television or home entertainment systems. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [121]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, silver. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its placement is lying flat on a surface, slightly tilted to one side. Its state is good condition, no obvious damage or wear. Its function is typical remote control for television or home entertainment systems. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [121]}, {"answers": ["typical remote control for television or home entertainment systems"], "object_ids": [121], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, silver. Its texture is smooth. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on a surface, slightly tilted to one side. Its state is good condition, no obvious damage or wear. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [121]}, {"answers": ["black, white, colorful patterns", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["shiny"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lying flat on a surface"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["in good condition"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["multifunctional, controls audio settings"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lying flat on a surface"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, colorful patterns. Its texture is shiny. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is in good condition. Its function is multifunctional, controls audio settings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [122]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, colorful patterns. Its texture is shiny. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its placement is lying flat on a surface. Its state is in good condition. Its function is multifunctional, controls audio settings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [122]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, colorful patterns. Its texture is shiny. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on a surface. Its state is in good condition. Its function is multifunctional, controls audio settings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [122]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [122], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black, white, colorful patterns. Its texture is shiny. Its material is plastic. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lying flat on a surface. Its state is in good condition. Its function is multifunctional, controls audio settings. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [122]}, {"answers": ["mostly black with colorful buttons", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["matte"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["sits flat on a surface"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["functioning properly"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["universal remote control with standard buttons for volume, channel, and navigation"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["functioning properly"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mostly black with colorful buttons. Its texture is matte. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is sits flat on a surface. Its function is universal remote control with standard buttons for volume, channel, and navigation. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [123]}, {"answers": ["universal remote control with standard buttons for volume, channel, and navigation"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mostly black with colorful buttons. Its texture is matte. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is sits flat on a surface. Its state is functioning properly. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [123]}, {"answers": ["mostly black with colorful buttons", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is matte. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is sits flat on a surface. Its state is functioning properly. Its function is universal remote control with standard buttons for volume, channel, and navigation. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [123]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [123], "object_names": ["remote control"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mostly black with colorful buttons. Its texture is matte. Its material is plastic. Its size is medium. Its placement is sits flat on a surface. Its state is functioning properly. Its function is universal remote control with standard buttons for volume, channel, and navigation. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [123]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft, velvety"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["microfiber or synthetic feather alternative", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright on the back of the couch"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition with no obvious signs of wear"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["providing support and comfort for anyone sitting on the couch"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is soft, velvety. Its material is microfiber or synthetic feather alternative. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the back of the couch. Its state is good condition with no obvious signs of wear. Its function is providing support and comfort for anyone sitting on the couch. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [124]}, {"answers": ["upright on the back of the couch"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft, velvety. Its material is microfiber or synthetic feather alternative. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition with no obvious signs of wear. Its function is providing support and comfort for anyone sitting on the couch. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [124]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft, velvety. Its material is microfiber or synthetic feather alternative. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the back of the couch. Its state is good condition with no obvious signs of wear. Its function is providing support and comfort for anyone sitting on the couch. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [124]}, {"answers": ["providing support and comfort for anyone sitting on the couch"], "object_ids": [124], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft, velvety. Its material is microfiber or synthetic feather alternative. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the back of the couch. Its state is good condition with no obvious signs of wear. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [124]}, {"answers": ["deep gray", "Gray"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft, plush"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["synthetic fabric (likely microfiber)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["slight incline on the sofa"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides support and comfort for sitting"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["slight incline on the sofa"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep gray. Its texture is soft, plush. Its material is synthetic fabric (likely microfiber). Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [131]}, {"answers": ["synthetic fabric (likely microfiber)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep gray. Its texture is soft, plush. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is slight incline on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [131]}, {"answers": ["soft, plush"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep gray. Its material is synthetic fabric (likely microfiber). Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is slight incline on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [131]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [131], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep gray. Its texture is soft, plush. Its material is synthetic fabric (likely microfiber). Its size is medium. Its placement is slight incline on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [131]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft and fluffy"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["microfiber or feather alternative", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright on the sofa"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides comfort and support on the sofa"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides comfort and support on the sofa"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft and fluffy. Its material is microfiber or feather alternative. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [132]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft and fluffy. Its material is microfiber or feather alternative. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its function is provides comfort and support on the sofa. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [132]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is soft and fluffy. Its material is microfiber or feather alternative. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides comfort and support on the sofa. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [132]}, {"answers": ["soft and fluffy"], "object_ids": [132], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its material is microfiber or feather alternative. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is provides comfort and support on the sofa. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [132]}, {"answers": ["dark", "Black"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["velvety"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft fabric (e.g. velvet)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["larger than a regular throw pillow, smaller than a big sofa cushion", "Medium"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright on the sofa"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["in good condition with no obvious signs of wear"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides comfort and support, complements the overall aesthetic of the room"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [133], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft fabric (e.g. velvet)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark. Its texture is velvety. Its size is larger than a regular throw pillow, smaller than a big sofa cushion. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is in good condition with no obvious signs of wear. Its function is provides comfort and support, complements the overall aesthetic of the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [133]}, {"answers": ["provides comfort and support, complements the overall aesthetic of the room"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark. Its texture is velvety. Its material is soft fabric (e.g. velvet). Its size is larger than a regular throw pillow, smaller than a big sofa cushion. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is in good condition with no obvious signs of wear. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [133]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark. Its texture is velvety. Its material is soft fabric (e.g. velvet). Its size is larger than a regular throw pillow, smaller than a big sofa cushion. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is in good condition with no obvious signs of wear. Its function is provides comfort and support, complements the overall aesthetic of the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [133]}, {"answers": ["larger than a regular throw pillow, smaller than a big sofa cushion", "Medium"], "object_ids": [133], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is dark. Its texture is velvety. Its material is soft fabric (e.g. velvet). Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is upright on the sofa. Its state is in good condition with no obvious signs of wear. Its function is provides comfort and support, complements the overall aesthetic of the room. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [133]}, {"answers": ["gray", "Gray"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft, plush"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft, plush material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertical on the sofa"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["excellent condition, no signs of wear or damage"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides additional support and comfort for sitting or lying down"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft, plush"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray. Its material is soft, plush material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its state is excellent condition, no signs of wear or damage. Its function is provides additional support and comfort for sitting or lying down. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [134]}, {"answers": ["excellent condition, no signs of wear or damage"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray. Its texture is soft, plush. Its material is soft, plush material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its function is provides additional support and comfort for sitting or lying down. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [134]}, {"answers": ["soft, plush material", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray. Its texture is soft, plush. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its state is excellent condition, no signs of wear or damage. Its function is provides additional support and comfort for sitting or lying down. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [134]}, {"answers": ["provides additional support and comfort for sitting or lying down"], "object_ids": [134], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is gray. Its texture is soft, plush. Its material is soft, plush material. Its size is moderate. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its state is excellent condition, no signs of wear or damage. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [134]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft, plushy"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cotton or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["square", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["center of the sofa"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["great condition"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["providing support and comfort for sitting"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [135], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["square", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft, plushy. Its material is cotton or similar fabric. Its size is medium-sized. Its placement is center of the sofa. Its state is great condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [135]}, {"answers": ["cotton or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft, plushy. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is square. Its placement is center of the sofa. Its state is great condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [135]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft, plushy. Its material is cotton or similar fabric. Its shape is square. Its placement is center of the sofa. Its state is great condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [135]}, {"answers": ["center of the sofa"], "object_ids": [135], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is soft, plushy. Its material is cotton or similar fabric. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is square. Its state is great condition. Its function is providing support and comfort for sitting. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [135]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [147], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [147], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [147], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [147], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [147], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its size is relatively small. Its placement is standing upright on the table. Its function is serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is plastic. Its size is relatively small. Its placement is standing upright on the table. Its function is serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is plastic. Its size is relatively small. Its function is serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147], "object_names": ["cup"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is plastic. Its placement is standing upright on the table. Its function is serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft plush. Its material is soft plush. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lies flat on the tiled floor. Its state is well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft plush. Its material is soft plush. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lies flat on the tiled floor. Its state is well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage. Its function is prevents slipping. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its texture is soft plush. Its material is soft plush. Its size is medium. Its placement is lies flat on the tiled floor. Its state is well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage. Its function is prevents slipping. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150], "object_names": ["carpet"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is deep blue. Its material is soft plush. Its size is medium. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is lies flat on the tiled floor. Its state is well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage. Its function is prevents slipping. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertical on the sofa"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["decorative, provides extra support or comfort"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard rectangular", "Medium"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is cotton blend. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is decorative, provides extra support or comfort. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [157]}, {"answers": ["cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its size is standard rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is decorative, provides extra support or comfort. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [157]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is cotton blend. Its size is standard rectangular. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its function is decorative, provides extra support or comfort. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [157]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [157], "object_names": ["pillow"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is blue. Its material is cotton blend. Its size is standard rectangular. Its placement is vertical on the sofa. Its state is good condition. Its function is decorative, provides extra support or comfort. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [157]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [159], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [159], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [159], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [159], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [159], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [159], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on the wall. Its state is good condition. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on the wall. Its state is good condition. Its function is decorative. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on the wall. Its function is decorative. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray. Its size is medium-sized. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is good condition. Its function is decorative. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["white, with a scene depicted in the painting", "White"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["canvas, wood (frame)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular, slightly larger than the painting", "Medium"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, no visible damage or wear"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["enhances the visual appeal of the wall"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["enhances the visual appeal of the wall"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white, with a scene depicted in the painting. Its texture is smooth. Its material is canvas, wood (frame). Its size is rectangular, slightly larger than the painting. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is well-preserved, no visible damage or wear. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, no visible damage or wear"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white, with a scene depicted in the painting. Its texture is smooth. Its material is canvas, wood (frame). Its size is rectangular, slightly larger than the painting. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its function is enhances the visual appeal of the wall. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["canvas, wood (frame)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white, with a scene depicted in the painting. Its texture is smooth. Its size is rectangular, slightly larger than the painting. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is well-preserved, no visible damage or wear. Its function is enhances the visual appeal of the wall. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["white, with a scene depicted in the painting", "White"], "object_ids": [161], "object_names": ["picture"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is canvas, wood (frame). Its size is rectangular, slightly larger than the painting. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is well-preserved, no visible damage or wear. Its function is enhances the visual appeal of the wall. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["black and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["synthetic materials (polyester fiber and rubber)", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["flat on the floor"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["providing comfort and support for walking or running"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic materials (polyester fiber and rubber). Its placement is flat on the floor. Its state is good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage. Its function is providing comfort and support for walking or running. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["flat on the floor"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic materials (polyester fiber and rubber). Its size is medium. Its state is good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage. Its function is providing comfort and support for walking or running. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["synthetic materials (polyester fiber and rubber)", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black and white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is medium. Its placement is flat on the floor. Its state is good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage. Its function is providing comfort and support for walking or running. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [162], "object_names": ["shoe"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is synthetic materials (polyester fiber and rubber). Its size is medium. Its placement is flat on the floor. Its state is good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage. Its function is providing comfort and support for walking or running. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["durable plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard adult-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["sleek, curved", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lying flat on a bed"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides protection during bicycle rides"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["durable plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its size is standard adult-sized. Its shape is sleek, curved. Its placement is lying flat on a bed. Its function is provides protection during bicycle rides. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [165]}, {"answers": ["standard adult-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is durable plastic. Its shape is sleek, curved. Its placement is lying flat on a bed. Its function is provides protection during bicycle rides. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [165]}, {"answers": ["sleek, curved", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is durable plastic. Its size is standard adult-sized. Its placement is lying flat on a bed. Its function is provides protection during bicycle rides. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [165]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [165], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is durable plastic. Its size is standard adult-sized. Its shape is sleek, curved. Its placement is lying flat on a bed. Its function is provides protection during bicycle rides. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [165]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light green-brown. Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its placement is hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall. Its state is neatly folded. Its function is convenient for drying hands. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall. Its state is neatly folded. Its function is convenient for drying hands. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light green-brown. Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is neatly folded. Its function is convenient for drying hands. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light green-brown. Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall. Its state is neatly folded. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["paper", "Paper"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["small", "Small"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["flat in the center on a wooden table"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["well-preserved"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["for writing or printing"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its material is paper. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is flat in the center on a wooden table. Its state is well-preserved. Its function is for writing or printing. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [172]}, {"answers": ["small", "Small"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is paper. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is flat in the center on a wooden table. Its state is well-preserved. Its function is for writing or printing. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [172]}, {"answers": ["flat in the center on a wooden table"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is paper. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is well-preserved. Its function is for writing or printing. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [172]}, {"answers": ["for writing or printing"], "object_ids": [172], "object_names": ["paper"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is paper. Its size is small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is flat in the center on a wooden table. Its state is well-preserved. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [172]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["shiny"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cylindrical", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["lying on the floor"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["resting flat"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["help people stay fit"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cylindrical", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is shiny. Its material is metal. Its weight is standard. Its size is standard. Its placement is lying on the floor. Its state is resting flat. Its function is help people stay fit. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [178]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is shiny. Its material is metal. Its weight is standard. Its size is standard. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is lying on the floor. Its state is resting flat. Its function is help people stay fit. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [178]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is shiny. Its material is metal. Its weight is standard. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is lying on the floor. Its state is resting flat. Its function is help people stay fit. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [178]}, {"answers": ["help people stay fit"], "object_ids": [178], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is shiny. Its material is metal. Its weight is standard. Its size is standard. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is lying on the floor. Its state is resting flat. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [178]}, {"answers": ["light beige", "White"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["off"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["controls the flow of electricity"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light beige. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is off. Its function is controls the flow of electricity. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [179]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light beige. Its material is plastic. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is off. Its function is controls the flow of electricity. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [179]}, {"answers": ["off"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light beige. Its material is plastic. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its function is controls the flow of electricity. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [179]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [179], "object_names": ["switch"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is light beige. Its material is plastic. Its size is relatively small. Its shape is rectangular. Its state is off. Its function is controls the flow of electricity. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [179]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is subtle checkered pattern. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on door handle. Its state is neatly hung. Its function is used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is subtle checkered pattern. Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on door handle. Its state is neatly hung. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is subtle checkered pattern. Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is hanging vertically on door handle. Its state is neatly hung. Its function is used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180], "object_names": ["towel"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is subtle checkered pattern. Its material is cotton or cotton blend. Its size is standard. Its placement is hanging vertically on door handle. Its state is neatly hung. Its function is used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["filled"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provides storage for used tableware"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is standard. Its placement is vertical. Its state is filled. Its function is provides storage for used tableware. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [182]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is filled. Its function is provides storage for used tableware. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [182]}, {"answers": ["filled"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is plastic. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its function is provides storage for used tableware. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [182]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [182], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its size is standard. Its shape is rectangular. Its placement is vertical. Its state is filled. Its function is provides storage for used tableware. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [182]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["ceramic or porcelain", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["sits flat on a tabletop"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["holding food"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round", "Circular"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is ceramic or porcelain. Its size is standard. Its placement is sits flat on a tabletop. Its state is good condition. Its function is holding food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [183]}, {"answers": ["ceramic or porcelain", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its shape is round. Its placement is sits flat on a tabletop. Its state is good condition. Its function is holding food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [183]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is ceramic or porcelain. Its size is standard. Its shape is round. Its placement is sits flat on a tabletop. Its function is holding food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [183]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [183], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is ceramic or porcelain. Its shape is round. Its placement is sits flat on a tabletop. Its state is good condition. Its function is holding food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [183]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["ceramic", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["round", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["sits flat on the countertop"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["holds a serving of food"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is ceramic. Its size is standard. Its shape is round. Its placement is sits flat on the countertop. Its function is holds a serving of food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [184]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its material is ceramic. Its size is standard. Its shape is round. Its placement is sits flat on the countertop. Its state is in great condition. Its function is holds a serving of food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [184]}, {"answers": ["sits flat on the countertop"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is ceramic. Its size is standard. Its shape is round. Its state is in great condition. Its function is holds a serving of food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [184]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [184], "object_names": ["bowl"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its material is ceramic. Its shape is round. Its placement is sits flat on the countertop. Its state is in great condition. Its function is holds a serving of food. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [184]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["cylindrical", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["new and unused"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["convenient for cleaning and wiping objects"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is new and unused. Its function is convenient for cleaning and wiping objects. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [186]}, {"answers": ["new and unused"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its shape is cylindrical. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its function is convenient for cleaning and wiping objects. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [186]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its shape is cylindrical. Its state is new and unused. Its function is convenient for cleaning and wiping objects. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [186]}, {"answers": ["cylindrical", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [186], "object_names": ["object"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is white. Its texture is smooth. Its size is standard. Its placement is hanging vertically on the wall. Its state is new and unused. Its function is convenient for cleaning and wiping objects. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [186]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is color of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is texture of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is material of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["light", "Light"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is weight of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["tall and slender", "Medium"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is size of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["vertical with a round base", "Conical"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is shape of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is placement of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is state of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["provide focused illumination"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["upright"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is smooth. Its material is metal. Its weight is light. Its size is tall and slender. Its shape is vertical with a round base. Its state is closed. Its function is provide focused illumination. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [189]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is smooth. Its material is metal. Its weight is light. Its size is tall and slender. Its shape is vertical with a round base. Its placement is upright. Its function is provide focused illumination. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [189]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its material is metal. Its weight is light. Its size is tall and slender. Its shape is vertical with a round base. Its placement is upright. Its state is closed. Its function is provide focused illumination. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [189]}, {"answers": ["provide focused illumination"], "object_ids": [189], "object_names": ["lamp"], "question": "I will give you a description of an item in the room:Its color is black. Its texture is smooth. Its material is metal. Its weight is light. Its size is tall and slender. Its shape is vertical with a round base. Its placement is upright. Its state is closed. What is function of this object?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [189]}]